citizentv.co.ke 2017-11-20

# Privacy Policy - Citizentv.co.ke

## Privacy Policy

Since your privacy is important to us, we provide this privacy statement explaining our online activity and the options you have on the way your information is collected and used our websites and mobile applications.

**Information We Collect**  
_Personally Identifiable Information_  
Some services in our site such as questionnaires, polls, competitions etc may request you to submit personally identifiable information about yourself. e.g name, e-mail address, telephone number etc in order to participate in such activities.

_Non-Personally Identifiable Information_  
We, advertisers, advertising networks, and our third party service providers may collect information that are anonymous or otherwise not intended to personally identify you when you visit Sites or using our Mobile Apps. Such information may include: network or Internet protocol address and type of browser you are using , the type of operating system you are using, the web pages you have visited, sites visited before and after you visit our site, the type of handheld or mobile device used to view our Site, general location information etc.

_Geo-location Information_  
If you are using our mobile app, you may be requested to share your geo-location information so that we can customize your experience on our app.

_Information from Social Networks_  
Through our third-party social media plugins, we may request you to allow our Site or app gain access to your social media accounts to allow you to access some services within the site/app e.g. Comment, Share articles, Engage with other users etc. Such a request will enable such services to have access to certain personally identifiable information and Non-Personally Identifiable Information from your social media profile (e.g., name, e-mail address, photo, gender, birthday, location, user files like photos and videos, your list of friends, people you follow and/or who follow you, the posts or the ‘likes’ you make, etc.).

**How We Use the Information**  
We may use the Information you provide us with to fulfill your requests for our, products/services, to respond to your inquiries about our offerings, to offer you other products or services that may be of interest to you etc.  
We may also use this information to communicate with you, e.g notify you when you have won a contests, to inform you of new products, send notifications and to collect feedback from you about our products or services.
